Finding Aid for the Alumni Relations Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Deceased Alumni
  - Jackson, James Douglas (Box 2698, Folder 57)
  - Jackson, James Truett (Box 2698, Folder 58)
  - Jackson, John Early (Box 2698, Folder 59)
  - Jackson, John McRenyolds and Rose Mary D. Jackson (Wife) (Box 2698, Folder 60)
  - Jackson, Kenneth McDonald (Box 2698, Folder 61)
  - Jackson, Kirby Erroll (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 2698, Folder 62)
  - Jackson, Kirby Erroll (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 2698, Folder 63)
  - Jackson, Milton Jacoby (Box 2698, Folder 64)
  - Jackson, Norman Erwin (Box 2698, Folder 65)
  - Jackson, Robert Charles and Evelyn June Burks (Wife) (Box 2698, Folder 66)
  - Jackson, Robert W. (Box 2698, Folder 67)
  - Jackson, Thomas Howard (Box 2698, Folder 68)
  - Jackson, Walter T. (Box 2698, Folder 69)
  - Jackson, Wayne Ward (Box 2698, Folder 70)
  - Jackson, Wesley M. (Box 2698, Folder 71)
  - Jacob, Gertrude F. (Box 2698, Folder 72)
  - Jacobs, David Lawrence (Box 2698, Folder 73)
  - Jacobs, J. Dillard (Box 2698, Folder 74)
  - Jacobs, M. Ted (Box 2698, Folder 75)
  - Jaggers, Craddock H. (Box 2698, Folder 76)
  - Jaggers, Roland F. (Box 2698, Folder 77)
  - Jakes, Richard Douglas, Photo (Box 2698, Folder 78)
  - Jakes, Robert (Box 2698, Folder 79)
  - James, David Hamilton (Box 2698, Folder 80)
  - James, Jesse Arvin (Box 2698, Folder 81)
  - Janowski, Jessie Edna Tucker (Box 2698, Folder 82)
  - Jared, Herbert Graham and Mary Katherine Douglas (Wife) (Box 2698, Folder 83)
  - Jarman, W. Maxey (Box 2699, Folder 1)
  - Jarratt, Porter Walton (Box 2699, Folder 2)
  - Jarratt, Waring B. (Box 2699, Folder 3)
  - Jarrell, Cecil Palmer (Box 2699, Folder 4)
  - Jarrell, Mary B. (Box 2699, Folder 5)
  - Jarrell, Monroe Lyman (Box 2699, Folder 6)
  - Jarrett, John H. (Box 2699, Folder 7)
  - Jasny, Tom (Box 2699, Folder 8)
  - Jasper, Dorothy Weinstein (Box 2699, Folder 9)
  - Javalera, Librada Topacio (Box 2699, Folder 10)
  - Jefferies, J. C. (Box 2699, Folder 11)
  - Jeffers, Kathryan Barber (Box 2699, Folder 12)
  - Jemison, Bessie D. (Box 2699, Folder 13)
  - Jenison, Garold Clairmont (Box 2699, Folder 14)
  - Jenkins, Delia M. Martin (Box 2699, Folder 15)
  - Jenkins, Edward Orestes (Box 2699, Folder 16)
  - Jenkins, Harry E., Photo (Box 2699, Folder 17)
  - Jenkins, Jesse Gee (Box 2699, Folder 18)
  - Jenkins, John Cameron (Box 2699, Folder 19)
  - Jennings, James Monroe and Ruby Braswell (Wife) (Box 2699, Folder 20)
  - Jennings, John H. (Box 2699, Folder 21)
  - Jennings, Lillian W. (Box 2699, Folder 22)
  - Jennings, Robert V. (Box 2699, Folder 23)
  - Jennings, T. V. (Box 2699, Folder 24)
  - Jennings, Tom P. (Box 2699, Folder 25)
  - Jerden, Carmine Clark (Box 2699, Folder 26)
  - Jernigan, John Albert (Box 2699, Folder 27)
  - Jernigan, Johnny Catherine (Box 2699, Folder 28)
  - Jernigan, William N. (Box 2699, Folder 29)
  - Jeter, William Emmet (Box 2699, Folder 30)
  - Jetton, Martha Lou Oakley (Mrs. Joe Hampton Jetton) (Box 2699, Folder 31)
  - Jew, Alice Wong (Mrs. Kim Foun Jew) (Box 2699, Folder 32)
  - Jewell, Asa Hickman (Box 2699, Folder 33)
  - Jewell, Charles W. and Sarah Ann Ridley (Wife) (Box 2699, Folder 34)
  - Jewell, John Berry (Box 2699, Folder 35)
  - Jewell, John J. (Box 2699, Folder 36)
  - Jewell, Richard (Box 2699, Folder 37)
  - Jewell, Willard B. (Box 2699, Folder 38)
  - Jewett, Hettie Moore (Box 2699, Folder 39)
  - Jobe, E. R. (Box 2699, Folder 40)
  - Jobe, Eugene Vance (Box 2699, Folder 41)
  - John, Roy (Box 2699, Folder 42)
  - Johns, Andrew Frank (Box 2699, Folder 43)
  - Johns, Paul Adkisson, Photo (Box 2699, Folder 44)
  - Johns, William Christy (Box 2699, Folder 45)
  - Johnson, Addie Mae Sadler (Box 2699, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, Ann Beasley (Box 2699, Folder 47)
  - Johnson, Betty Ann Thice (Box 2699, Folder 48)
  - Johnson, Burnice Alexander (Box 2699, Folder 49)
  - Johnson, Charles DeWitt (Box 2699, Folder 50)
  - Johnson, Charles Williamson (Box 2699, Folder 51)
  - Johnson, Claud Dinkins (Box 2699, Folder 52)
  - Johnson, David Foote Sellers (Box 2699, Folder 53)
  - Johnson, Edward Eugene (Box 2699, Folder 54)
  - Johnson, Ela Eglantine (Box 2699, Folder 55)
  - Johnson, Elizabeth Cody (Box 2699, Folder 56)
  - Johnson, Elsie Marie (Box 2699, Folder 57)
  - Johnson, Eugene Harris (Box 2699, Folder 58)
  - Johnson, Eugenia Morton Covington (Mrs. H. Dwight Johnson) (Box 2699, Folder 59)
  - Johnson, Fay (Box 2699, Folder 60)
  - Johnson, Fredia (Box 2699, Folder 61)
  - Johnson, George E., Photo (Box 2699, Folder 62)
  - Johnson, H. Dwight (Box 2699, Folder 63)
  - Johnson, Harry R. (Box 2699, Folder 64)
  - Johnson, Hattie Jenkins (Box 2699, Folder 65)
  - Johnson, Hubert Vernon, Photo (Box 2699, Folder 66)
  - Johnson, James Leo (Box 2699, Folder 67)
  - Johnson, James Paul and Ruth McCampbell Owsley (Wife) (Box 2699, Folder 68)
  - Johnson, James Wilson (Box 2699, Folder 69)
  - Johnson, Jane Mcmahon Gaines (Mrs. Ralph W. Johnson) (Box 2699, Folder 70)
  - Johnson, Jean Ruth Nolan (Box 2699, Folder 71)
  - Johnson, Jerry Becker, Photo (Box 2699, Folder 72)
  - Johnson, John Willard (Box 2699, Folder 73)
  - Johnson, L. Clarke (Box 2699, Folder 74)
  - Johnson, Lester Elmer (Box 2699, Folder 75)
  - Johnson, Lucy Wood (Box 2699, Folder 76)
  - Johnson, Mary Elizabeth (Box 2699, Folder 77)
  - Johnson, Myrtle Eugenia Pope (Mrs. J. O. Johnson) (Box 2699, Folder 78)
  - Johnson, Pickers (Box 2699, Folder 79)
  - Johnson, Richard Akin (Box 2699, Folder 80)
  - Johnson, Robert Leland (Box 2699, Folder 81)
  - Johnson, Samuel A. (Box 2699, Folder 82)
  - Johnson, Samuel Earle, Photo (Box 2699, Folder 83)
  - Johnson, Sara Elizabeth Cody (Box 2699, Folder 84)
  - Johnson, Stanley P. (Box 2699, Folder 85)
  - Johnson, William Andrew (Box 2699, Folder 86)
  - Johnson, William W. (Box 2699, Folder 87)
  - Johnson, Willoughby H. (Box 2699, Folder 88)
  - Johnson, Woodrow Wilson (Box 2699, Folder 89)
  - Johnston, Chambless Rand and Anita C. Ofallon (Wife) (Box 2699, Folder 90)
  - Johnston, Charles G. (Box 2699, Folder 91)
  - Johnston, Douglas (Box 2699, Folder 92)
  - Johnston, Hugh Halason (Box 2699, Folder 93)
  - Johnston, John Davis (Box 2699, Folder 94)
  - Johnston, John Deveraux (Box 2699, Folder 95)
  - Johnston, Mack Neil (Box 2699, Folder 96)
  - Jolley, Cola Nelson (Box 2699, Folder 97)
  - Jolly, David (Box 2699, Folder 98)
  - Jones, Anne Dunbar (Box 2699, Folder 99)
  - Jones, Arthur Heath (Box 2699, Folder 100)
  - Jones, Benjamin Franklin (Box 2699, Folder 101)
  - Jones, Brooks (Box 2699, Folder 102)
  - Jones, Charles Clay (Box 2699, Folder 103)
  - Jones, Charles Scarritt, Photo (Box 2699, Folder 104)
  - Jones, Dallas Jackson (Box 2699, Folder 105)
  - Jones, David L. (Box 2699, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Donahey H. (Box 2699, Folder 107)
  - Jones, Dorothy Hope (Box 2699, Folder 108)
  - Jones, Dudley K. (Box 2699, Folder 109)
  - Jones, Earl (Box 2699, Folder 110)
  - Jones, Edgar (Box 2699, Folder 111)
  - Jones, Edward V. (Box 2699, Folder 112)
  - Jones, Ella Ree, Photo (Box 2699, Folder 113)
  - Jones, Eloise C. Ogilvie (Mrs. Edward Oscar Jones) (Box 2699, Folder 114)
  - Jones, Ernest Paul (Box 2699, Folder 115)
  - Jones, Fannye M. (Box 2699, Folder 116)
  - Jones, Flossie Adele (Box 2699, Folder 117)
  - Jones, Frank E. (Box 2699, Folder 118)
  - Jones, G. S. (Box 2699, Folder 119)
  - Jones, Garland Frank (Box 2699, Folder 120)
  - Jones, George Simpson (Box 2699, Folder 121)
  - Jones, H. Parks and Anne Underwood (Wife) (Box 2699, Folder 122)
  - Jones, Harold C. (Box 2699, Folder 123)
  - Jones, Harry Douglas (Box 2699, Folder 124)
  - Jones, Harry Henderson (Box 2699, Folder 125)
  - Jones, Harry Shelton (Box 2699, Folder 126)
  - Jones, Henry Hart (Box 2699, Folder 127)
  - Jones, Herbert Vincent (Box 2699, Folder 128)
  - Jones, Herman Douglas (Box 2699, Folder 129)
  - Jones, Horace Grady (Box 2699, Folder 130)
  - Jones, Isaac Grady (Box 2699, Folder 131)
  - Jones, James Land (Box 2700, Folder 1)
  - Jones, James Vickers (Box 2700, Folder 2)
  - Jones, John Price (Box 2700, Folder 3)
  - Jones, Josephine Wemyss (Mrs. J. Mackinlay Jones) (Box 2700, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Lofton Brodie, Photo (Box 2700, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Margaret Louis (Box 2700, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Mary M. (Box 2700, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Mary Sneed (Box 2700, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Meredith Cabell (Box 2700, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Orrin Lester (Box 2700, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Ransom (Box 2700, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Richard Jesse (Box 2700, Folder 12)
  - Jones, Robert Leonard (Box 2700, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Stuart C. (Box 2700, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Vivian Dodd Moore (Mrs. Thomas Fay Jones) (Box 2700, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Waruene (Box 2700, Folder 16)
  - Jones, Wesley Fletcher and Helen Rebecca White (Wife) (Box 2700, Folder 17)
  - Jones, Willard Von, Photo (Box 2700, Folder 18)
  - Jones, William Alton, Photo (Box 2700, Folder 19)
  - Jones, William F. (D. 1913) (Box 2700, Folder 20)
  - Jones, William F. (B.A. 1961), Photo (Box 2700, Folder 21)
  - Jones, William Thomas (Box 2700, Folder 22)
  - Jones, Wilson Pettibone, Photo (Box 2700, Folder 23)
  - Jordan, Clyde W. (Box 2700, Folder 24)
  - Jordan, Emily Lucille Luck (Mrs. Henry Preston Jordan) (Box 2700, Folder 25)
  - Jordan, Evelyn Ward (Box 2700, Folder 26)
  - Jordan, Florence Neil (Box 2700, Folder 27)
  - Jordan, Leland Walker (Box 2700, Folder 28)
  - Jordan, Pauline (Box 2700, Folder 29)
  - Jordan, William King (Box 2700, Folder 30)
  - Joselyn, Irene Dorothy Milliken (Box 2700, Folder 31)
  - Joseph, Clay Evans (Box 2700, Folder 32)
  - Joslin, Lucy (Box 2700, Folder 33)
  - Judd, Romie Dustin (Box 2700, Folder 34)
  - Julian, Margaret Eller (Box 2700, Folder 35)
  - Julufka, Earl (Box 2700, Folder 36)
  - Jurjevich, Joseph C. (Box 2700, Folder 37)
  - Karnes, Houston Thurman (Box 2700, Folder 38)
  - Kaylor, Ada Ethel (Box 2700, Folder 39)
  - Keene, Jesse Lin and Helen Rose Keene (Wife), Photo (Box 2700, Folder 40)
  - Keene, Victor A. (Box 2700, Folder 41)
  - Keeton, John R. (Box 2700, Folder 42)
  - Kelley, John Wayne and Page Edgerton (Wife), Tennessee State Representative (Box 2700, Folder 43)
  - Kemp, Augusta Hasslock (Box 2700, Folder 44)
  - Kendall, Douglas Warren (Box 2700, Folder 45)
  - Kennedy, Eva C. (Box 2700, Folder 46)
  - Keso, Edward, Photo (Box 2700, Folder 47)
  - Keyes, Thomas Logan (Box 2700, Folder 48)
  - Kidd, Kenneth Paul (Box 2700, Folder 49)
  - King, Anna M. (Box 2700, Folder 50)
  - Kinser, Wesley Luther (Box 2700, Folder 51)
  - Kirkman, Caswell Macon (Box 2700, Folder 52)
  - Klein, Arthur Francis (Box 2700, Folder 53)
  - Koehler, John Omer (Box 2700, Folder 54)
  - Kohut, Gladys Jackson (Box 2700, Folder 55)
  - Kuehn, Herbert Fredrick (Box 2700, Folder 56)
  - Kyle, Roy E. and Sara Shefield (Wife) (Box 2700, Folder 57)
  - Lacey, William Henry (Box 2700, Folder 58)
  - Lackey, Carver Morton (Box 2700, Folder 59)
  - Lambeth, Douglas Spruill (Box 2700, Folder 60)
  - Lampe, Stuart E., Photo (Box 2700, Folder 61)
  - Lancaster, James Caruthers (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 2700, Folder 62)
  - Lancaster, James Caruthers (Folder 2 of 3), Photo (Box 2700, Folder 63)
  - Lancaster, James Caruthers (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 2700, Folder 64)
  - Landis, Jeanne (Box 2700, Folder 65)
  - Lane, James Butler (Box 2700, Folder 66)
  - Lane, Marion P. (Box 2700, Folder 67)
  - Lanier, Alfred C. (Box 2700, Folder 68)
  - Lanning, Adam B. (Box 2700, Folder 69)
  - Lanning, Adam B., III (Box 2700, Folder 70)
  - Largen, William A. (Box 2700, Folder 71)
  - Laurence, E. Mallinckrodt (Box 2700, Folder 72)
  - Lawrence, Joseph Pinckney and Martha Noel Eates Keeble (Wife) (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 2700, Folder 73)
  - Lawrence, Joseph Pinckney and Martha Noel Eates Keeble (Wife) (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 2700, Folder 74)
  - Lawrence, Robert Landy (Box 2700, Folder 75)
  - Lawton, Alice Stockton (Box 2700, Folder 76)
  - Layton, William Isaac and Eva Wade (Wife) (Box 2700, Folder 77)
  - Leacock, Rose A. (Box 2700, Folder 78)
  - Lee, Cora K. (Box 2700, Folder 79)
  - Lee, Robert Edward (Box 2700, Folder 80)
  - Leech, William M. (Box 2700, Folder 81)
  - Lemert, Harry (Box 2700, Folder 82)
  - Lerosen, Wesley Alexander (Box 2700, Folder 83)
  - Lewis, John A. (Box 2700, Folder 84)
  - Lindsay, Pauline Garard (Mrs. Lewis Preston Lindsay) (Box 2700, Folder 85)
  - Line, Sara Jane (Box 2700, Folder 86)
  - Lipscomb, Henry Zellner (Box 2700, Folder 87)
  - Lipscomb, Horace Swift (Box 2700, Folder 88)
  - Little, Julian R. (Box 2700, Folder 89)
  - Long, Frances Caroline (Box 2700, Folder 90)
  - Long, Joseph K. (Box 2700, Folder 91)
  - Lunn, Clyde Donald (Box 2700, Folder 92)
  - Luton, James Allen (Box 2700, Folder 93)
  - McBride, Otis (Box 2700, Folder 94)
  - McCall, Gertrude Linden Lewis (Mrs. John T. McCall) (Box 2700, Folder 95)
  - McClanahan, Jerry Warner (Box 2700, Folder 96)
  - McClanahan, John W. (Box 2700, Folder 97)
  - McClary, Richard Ellis and Mary Ann Harrison (Wife) (Box 2700, Folder 98)
  - McDonald, Leon (Box 2700, Folder 99)
  - McDonald, Ruth G. (Box 2700, Folder 100)
  - McGavock, Sarah Herbert Nolan (Box 2700, Folder 101)
  - McGaw, Anita June Moody (Box 2700, Folder 102)
  - McGunnis, Howard J. (Box 2700, Folder 103)
  - McGlothlin, William Grady, Photo (Box 2700, Folder 104)
  - McKay, Douglas Edward (Box 2701, Folder 1)
  - McKay, Kate Curtis (Box 2701, Folder 2)
  - McLemore, Nannie P. (Box 2701, Folder 3)
  - McMillan, Thomas H. (Box 2701, Folder 4)
  - McMinn, John H. (Box 2701, Folder 5)
  - McMullan, Lois (Box 2701, Folder 6)
  - Maddux, David Douglas (Box 2701, Folder 7)
  - Maffet, Thelma Eliz (Box 2701, Folder 8)
  - Mahon, Robert Perry and Jasca Rose Williamson (Wife) (Box 2701, Folder 9)
  - Maiden, Lewis Smith and Leota Stultz Driver (Wife) (Box 2701, Folder 10)
  - Malone, Dandridge Michael, Photo (Box 2701, Folder 11)
  - Manley, Russel E. (Box 2701, Folder 12)
  - Manchester, Paul Thomas (Box 2701, Folder 13)
  - Manners, Louie Thomas and Nelle Marie Julian (Wife) (Box 2701, Folder 14)
  - Mansker, Katy Lee (Box 2701, Folder 15)
  - Manuszak, Raymond Anthony (Box 2701, Folder 16)
  - Markus, Frits (Box 2701, Folder 17)
  - Marlin, George William (Box 2701, Folder 18)
  - Marquis, Benjamin (Box 2701, Folder 19)
  - Marsh, William Hollister (Box 2701, Folder 20)
  - Martin, Allie Beth Dent (Box 2701, Folder 21)
  - Martin, Carl Taylor (Box 2701, Folder 22)
  - Martin, Caroline Lewis Penrod (Box 2701, Folder 23)
  - Martin, Charles Louis (Box 2701, Folder 24)
  - Martin, Elaine (Mrs. Noel Preston Martin) (Box 2701, Folder 25)
  - Martin, Homer Otis, Photo (Box 2701, Folder 26)
  - Martin, Jon W. (Box 2701, Folder 27)
  - Martin, Minna Cunningham and Edwin T. (Box 2701, Folder 28)
  - Martin, Richard Thomas (Box 2701, Folder 29)
  - Martin, Robert Beecher (Box 2701, Folder 30)
  - Martin, Rose Rich Breyer, Photo (Box 2701, Folder 31)
  - Mason, Beatryce Robinson (Box 2701, Folder 32)
  - Mathes, Robert Louis and Kathryn Lee King (Wife) (Box 2701, Folder 33)
  - Matthews, Ernest Crawford (Box 2701, Folder 34)
  - Matthews, Katherine (Box 2701, Folder 35)
  - Maurer, Frances Sheffield (Box 2701, Folder 36)
  - May, Frank Henry, Photo (Box 2701, Folder 37)
  - May, Lynn E., Photo (Box 2701, Folder 38)
  - Means, Marie Hackl (Box 2701, Folder 39)
  - Meyer, F. Eileen (Box 2701, Folder 40)
  - Miles, Howard Ellswood (Box 2701, Folder 41)
  - Miller, Charles Fred and Anne Lewis (Wife) (Box 2701, Folder 42)
  - Miller, Cleo and Kathryn Cotten Miller (Wife) (Box 2701, Folder 43)
  - Miller, James S. (Box 2701, Folder 44)
  - Miller, Leora (Box 2701, Folder 45)
  - Milliken, Margaret Steele (Box 2701, Folder 46)
  - Mintzer, Marion Elizabeth Head (Mrs. Olin Wesley Mintzer) (Box 2701, Folder 47)
  - Mitchell, Morris R. (Box 2701, Folder 48)
  - Mitchell, Robert Scott (Box 2701, Folder 49)
  - Modlin, Ruth (Box 2701, Folder 50)
  - Montgomery, Joseph B. (Box 2701, Folder 51)
  - Montgomery, Samuel Shannon (Box 2701, Folder 52)
  - Moore, Patricia McClintock (Mrs. Arthur Raymond Moore) (Box 2701, Folder 53)
  - Morgan, William Horace, Photo (Box 2701, Folder 54)
  - Morrow, Sarah O. (Box 2701, Folder 55)
  - Morse, Mary Emma (Box 2701, Folder 56)
  - Morton, John T. (Box 2701, Folder 57)
  - Moss, Charles Malcolm (Folder 1 of 4) (Box 2701, Folder 58)
  - Moss, Charles Malcolm (Folder 2 of 4) (Box 2701, Folder 59)
  - Moss, Charles Malcolm (Folder 3 of 4) (Box 2701, Folder 60)
  - Moss, Charles Malcolm (Folder 4 of 4), Photo (Box 2701, Folder 61)
  - Moss, Charles Smith (Box 2701, Folder 62)
  - Moss, William Preston (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 2701, Folder 63)
  - Moss, William Preston (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 2701, Folder 64)
  - Motter, David C. (Box 2701, Folder 65)
  - Mueller, Max William (Box 2701, Folder 66)
  - Murphey, Francis (Box 2701, Folder 67)
  - Murphy, Abbie Scott Vaughn, Photo (Box 2701, Folder 68)
  - Murphy, Robert Jennings (Box 2701, Folder 69)
  - Murray, Louis Joseph (Box 2701, Folder 70)
  - Murrell, Charles Dandridge (Box 2701, Folder 71)
  - Muse, Albert Lester (Box 2701, Folder 72)
  - Myers, George R. (Box 2701, Folder 73)
  - Napier, Amelia Kerr (Box 2701, Folder 74)
  - Neville, Charles Willis (Box 2701, Folder 75)
  - Neville, Charles Willis (Junior) (Box 2701, Folder 76)
  - Newman, James Marion (Box 2701, Folder 77)
  - Newman, Lela Carr (Box 2701, Folder 78)
  - Newman, Linda Evelyn (Box 2701, Folder 79)
  - Nicholson, Beverly Jane Davis (Mrs. Alexander Macdonald Nicholson) (Box 2701, Folder 80)
  - Nicholson, Jane A. (Box 2701, Folder 81)
  - Nicholson, William B. (Box 2702, Folder 1)
  - Nimmerfall, Mary Park Sullivant (Box 2702, Folder 2)
  - Nixon, Anne Richardson Trice (Mrs. Herman Clarence Nixon) (Box 2702, Folder 3)
  - Noojin, Ray Oscar (Box 2702, Folder 4)
  - Norgress, Rachel E. (Box 2702, Folder 5)
  - Oakley, Bethel Beulah (Box 2702, Folder 6)
  - O'Brien, Philip Joseph (Box 2702, Folder 7)
  - O'Donnel, William Joseph (Box 2702, Folder 8)
  - Omohundro, John Moten (Box 2702, Folder 9)
  - O'Neal, Ouida M. (Box 2702, Folder 10)
  - O'Rear, Ruby Alberta (Box 2702, Folder 11)
  - Orgain, Harry H. (Box 2702, Folder 12)
  - Ousley, Odille (Box 2702, Folder 13)
  - Owen, Dewitt (Box 2702, Folder 14)
  - Owen, Mabel McNichols (Box 2702, Folder 15)
  - Owen, William Hunter (Box 2702, Folder 16)
  - Ozment, James G. (Box 2702, Folder 17)
  - Paden, William (Box 2702, Folder 18)
  - Panigot, Helen Louise (Box 2702, Folder 19)
  - Parker, Benjamin F., Photo (Box 2702, Folder 20)
  - Parker, Betty Claire Jacobs (Mrs. Steven M. Parker), Photo (Box 2702, Folder 21)
  - Parker, Ira Edward (Box 2702, Folder 22)
  - Parkes, James Hanner (Box 2702, Folder 23)
  - Parnell, R. Lanier and Irene (Wife) (Box 2702, Folder 24)
  - Parrish, Walter Mason and Mary Fulks (Wife) (Box 2702, Folder 25)
  - Pate, Zeph Eugenia, Photo (Box 2702, Folder 26)
  - Payne, Bruce Rayburn (Box 2702, Folder 27)
  - Payne, William Harold, Peabody President (Box 2702, Folder 28)
  - Peach, Patsy Faye Welch (Box 2702, Folder 29)
  - Pear, Moe (Box 2702, Folder 30)
  - Pearson, Barbara Anne Stone (Mrs. Lynn Dow Pearson) (Box 2702, Folder 31)
  - Pearson, Mary Katherine Fleeman (Mrs. William Martin Pearson) (Box 2702, Folder 32)
  - Peavy, Henry Jackson (Box 2702, Folder 33)
  - Peavy, Hubert Daniel (Box 2702, Folder 34)
  - Peay, Charles Head (Box 2702, Folder 35)
  - Peck, Herbert Jefferson, Photo (Box 2702, Folder 36)
  - Peck, Virginia Lewis (Box 2702, Folder 37)
  - Pedigo, James Monroe (Box 2702, Folder 38)
  - Peebles, Arnold (Box 2702, Folder 39)
  - Peebles, Thomas H. and Grace Waverlyn Jackson (Wife) (Box 2702, Folder 40)
  - Peebles, William Rives (Box 2702, Folder 41)
  - Peede, Robert Louis (Box 2702, Folder 42)
  - Peeler, Elizabeth Hastings (Box 2702, Folder 43)
  - Peeler, Leonard W. (Box 2702, Folder 44)
  - Peerson, Nell (Box 2702, Folder 45)
  - Peery, James Lea (Box 2702, Folder 46)
  - Penick, Roland Wingate (Box 2702, Folder 47)
  - Penland, George William (Box 2702, Folder 48)
  - Penn, Ruth Warmbrod (Box 2702, Folder 49)
  - Pennington, George Lewis (Box 2702, Folder 50)
  - Pennington, James Augustus (Box 2702, Folder 51)
  - Pennock, Laurel M. (Box 2702, Folder 52)
  - Pentecost, J. W. (Box 2702, Folder 53)
  - Peoples, James A. (Box 2702, Folder 54)
  - Peoples, Joe Webb (Box 2702, Folder 55)
  - Pepper, Stanton A. (Box 2702, Folder 56)
  - Pepper, William Louis (Box 2702, Folder 57)
  - Perdue, Doran Ellis (Box 2702, Folder 58)
  - Pereda, Eugene Falero (Box 2702, Folder 59)
  - Perkins, Roy Oakland (Box 2702, Folder 60)
  - Perl, Samuel David (Box 2702, Folder 61)
  - Perry, Catherine E. (Box 2702, Folder 62)
  - Perry, Frank F. (Box 2702, Folder 63)
  - Perry, Raymond Harlan (Box 2702, Folder 64)
  - Perry, Robert M. (Box 2702, Folder 65)
  - Pershing, Madeline (Box 2702, Folder 66)
  - Person, Virginia Elizabeth Douglass (Box 2702, Folder 67)
  - Peter, Lily (Folder 1 of 2), Photo; Poet (Box 2702, Folder 68)
  - Peter, Lily (Folder 2 of 2), Photo; Poet (Box 2702, Folder 69)
  - Peters, Fredrick Todd (Box 2702, Folder 70)
  - Peters, Horace Dewey, Photo (Box 2702, Folder 71)
  - Peterson, Adelaide Gaines Douglas (Mrs. Reuben Ervin Peterson) (Box 2702, Folder 72)
  - Peterson, Merlin Dewey (Box 2702, Folder 73)
  - Phelps, Carlyle Randolph (Box 2702, Folder 74)
  - Phillipp, Louis Samuel (Box 2702, Folder 75)
  - Phillips, Myrtle Baars (Box 2703, Folder 1)
  - Pierce, Philip Early (Box 2703, Folder 2)
  - Pierson, Alvan R. (Box 2703, Folder 3)
  - Pigg, Charles Eugene (Box 2703, Folder 4)
  - Pinkston, David Michael (Box 2703, Folder 5)
  - Pinson, Joe N. (Box 2703, Folder 6)
  - Polk, Cadwallader L. (Box 2703, Folder 7)
  - Polk, Greenfield Quarles and Maxine Wilson (Wife), Photo (Box 2703, Folder 8)
  - Polk, James Walter and Hazel Killmagsworth (Wife) (Box 2703, Folder 9)
  - Polk, Laurence Norton and Marjorie Lee Shapard (Wife) (Box 2703, Folder 10)
  - Polk, Lillian Johnson (Box 2703, Folder 11)
  - Polk, Vivan (Box 2703, Folder 12)
  - Polk, Winfred D., Photo (Box 2703, Folder 13)
  - Pomeranz, Alfred Abraham (Box 2703, Folder 14)
  - Pommerening, Nancy Ann Johnson (Mrs. Glen E. Pommering) (Box 2703, Folder 15)
  - Ponturo, Dominick William, Photo (Box 2703, Folder 16)
  - Pool, Yelton (Box 2703, Folder 17)
  - Poole, Everett B. (Box 2703, Folder 18)
  - Poret, George Cleveland (Box 2703, Folder 19)
  - Porter, Cheairs Mays (Box 2703, Folder 20)
  - Porter, Eugenia (Box 2703, Folder 21)
  - Porter, Gertrude R. (Box 2703, Folder 22)
  - Porter, James Otey, Photo (Box 2703, Folder 23)
  - Porter, William Clayton (Box 2703, Folder 24)
  - Potter, Edward (Box 2703, Folder 25)
  - Powell, Robert F. (Box 2703, Folder 26)
  - Powers, Donald L. (Box 2703, Folder 27)
  - P'Pool, Harold (Box 2703, Folder 28)
  - Preston, Will Manier and Eunice Lannon (Wife) (Folder 1 of 2), Photo (Box 2703, Folder 29)
  - Preston, Will Manier and Eunice Lannon (Wife) (Folder 2 of 2), Photo (Box 2703, Folder 30)
  - Preston, William Owen and Alice Moynihan (Wife) (Box 2703, Folder 31)
  - Price, George W. (Box 2703, Folder 32)
  - Pritchett, Margaret Elizabeth (Box 2703, Folder 33)
  - Proctor, Frank Scott, Photo (Box 2703, Folder 34)
  - Provost, Frank Pierce, Photo (Box 2703, Folder 35)
  - Puryear, Sarah Frances (Box 2703, Folder 36)
  - Putnam, John F. (Box 2703, Folder 37)
  - Ragsdale, Clifton Alexander and Vada L. Wilson (Wife) (Box 2703, Folder 38)
  - Rainey, John F. (Box 2703, Folder 39)
  - Ralston, West Morton (Box 2703, Folder 40)
  - Ramsey, Tracy Webb (Box 2703, Folder 41)
  - Randolph, Arthur Cole (Box 2703, Folder 42)
  - Randolph, William P. (Box 2703, Folder 43)
  - Ray, Dennie Allie (Box 2703, Folder 44)
  - Ray, Dennie Ezell (Box 2703, Folder 45)
  - Rea, Robert Cresswell (Box 2703, Folder 46)
  - Redeman, William Anthony (Box 2703, Folder 47)